const unit7Problems = [{
    //--------------------------------------------SECTION 7.1 ----------------------------------
        //13
        id: 161,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int \\>{\\it x}^3({\\it x}^4+3)^2 \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "(x^4+3)^3/12 + C",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.1",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //17
        id: 162,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int \\>{\\it x} \\sqrt{{\\it x}^2 + 2} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "(x^2+2)^(3/2)/3 + C",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.1",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //21
        id: 163,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int \\> \\dfrac{7 \\it x}{(1-{\\it x}^2)^3} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "7/(4(1-x^2)^2) + C",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.1",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //41
        id: 164,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int \\> \\cos 6 \\it x \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "1/6 sin 6x + C",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.1",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //61
        id: 165,
        question: "Evaluate the definite integral $ \\int_{-1}^{\\>1} \\> {\\it x} ({\\it x}^2+1)^3 \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "0",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.1",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    },
    //--------------------------------------------SECTION 7.2 ----------------------------------
    {
        //9
        id: 166,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int \\> \\dfrac {\\it x} {{\\it x}^2-3} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "1/2 ln|x^2 - 3| + C",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.2",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //29
        id: 167,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int \\> \\dfrac {1} {1+ \\sqrt{2{\\it x}}} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "sqrt 2x - ln(1 + sqrt 2x) + C",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.2",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //53
        id: 168,
        question: "Evaluate the definite integral $ \\int_{1}^{\\>e} \\> \\dfrac {(1+ \\ln {\\it x})^2} {{\\it x}} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "7/3",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.2",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //99
        id: 169,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int \\> \\dfrac {e^{-\\it x}} {1+e^{-\\it x}} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "x - ln(e^x + 1) + C",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.2",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //125
        id: 170,
        question: "Find the area of the region bounded by the graphs of the equations ${\\it y} = {\\it xe}^{-{\\it x}^2/4}$, ${\\it y} = 0$, ${\\it x} = 0$, and ${\\it x} = \\sqrt 6$. Round your answer to the nearest 3 decimal places.",
        answer: "1.554",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.2",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    },
    //--------------------------------------------SECTION 7.3 ----------------------------------
    {
        //11
        id: 171,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int \\> \\dfrac {\\it x} {{\\it x}^4+25} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "1/10 arctan(t^2/5) + C",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.3",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //23
        id: 172,
        question: "Evaluate the definite integral $ \\int_{0}^{1/6} \\> \\dfrac {3} {\\sqrt {1-9{\\it x}^2}} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "pi/6",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.3",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //31
        id: 173,
        question: "Evaluate the definite integral $ \\int_{\\pi /2}^{\\pi} \\> \\dfrac {\\sin \\it x} {1+\\cos ^2 \\it x} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "pi/4",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.3",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //29
        id: 174,
        question: "Evaluate the definite integral $ \\int_{0}^{\\ln 5} \\> \\dfrac {\\it e^x} {1+\\it e^{2x}} \\,\\it dx$. Round your answer to the nearest 3 decimal places.",
        answer: "0.588",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.3",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    },  {
        //33
        id: 175,
        question: "Evaluate the definite integral $ \\int_{0}^{1/\\sqrt 2} \\> \\dfrac {\\arcsin \\it x} {\\sqrt {1-{\\it x}^2}} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "pi^2/32",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.3",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    },   {
        //35
        id: 176,
        question: "Evaluate the definite integral $ \\int_{0}^{2} \\> \\dfrac {1} {{\\it x}^2 -2{\\it x} + 2} \\,\\it dx$. (Hint: Complete the square.)",
        answer: "pi/2",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.3",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, 
    //--------------------------------------------SECTION 7.4 ----------------------------------
    {
        //21
        id: 177,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int \\> \\dfrac {{\\it x}^2-3} {-{\\it x}^3 +9{\\it x} + 1} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "-1/3 ln|-x^3 + 9x + 1| + C",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.4",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //25
        id: 178,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int \\> \\dfrac {{\\it x}+2} {{\\it x}+1} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "x + ln|x + 1| + C",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.4",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //33
        id: 179,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int \\> \\dfrac {2} {e^{-{\\it x}}+1} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "2 ln(1 + e^x) + C",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.4",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //41
        id: 180,
        question: "Find the indefinite integral $ \\int \\> \\dfrac {\\tan ({2/\\it x})} {{\\it x}^2} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "1/2 ln|cos 2/t| + C",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.4",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //65
        id: 181,
        question: "Evaluate the definite integral $ \\int_{0}^{8} \\> \\dfrac {2{\\it x}} {\\sqrt {{\\it x}^2+36}} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "8",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.4",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //69
        id: 182,
        question: "Evaluate the definite integral $ \\int_{0}^{2/\\sqrt 3} \\> \\dfrac {1} {4+9{\\it x}^2} \\,\\it dx$.",
        answer: "pi/18",
        unit: 7,
        topic: "7.4",
        tags: ["Integrals"],
        solution: "sample solution"
    },
];
    
    export default unit7Problems;